Serhat Yavuzyigit

Senior Computer Engineering Student

Address: Ankara, Turkey WWW: github.com/serhatyavuzyigit

E-mail: soyavuzyigit@gmail.com

Motivated student completing Computer Engineering degree. Gained experience with two long term internships in software development. Experienced in Agile and Scrum environments. Supports team members with the project, design and programming needs. Fluent in English and Turkish. Want to contribute to the world for became a better place. Want to proof myself in big tech companies.

Education

2016-09 - Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

TOBB University Of Economics And Technology - Ankara, Turkey

GPA: 3.02 / 4.0

• Courses Taken: Data Structures, Algorithms, Software Engineering, Computer Graphics, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning...

Work Experience

2019-01 - Software Engineer Intern

2020-04 SimBT, Ankara, Turkey

- Worked with a scrum team in defense industry software engineering project.
- · Contributed to project with bugfixes, improvements and refactoring the code.
- · Gained experience with Java, Java FX and Maven.

2019-09 - **Software Engineer Intern**

2019-12

AYESAS, Ankara, Turkey

- Worked with a software engineering project team.
- Gained experience in avionics software development and Microsoft Visual Studio environment.
- Developed a tool using C++ and OT.

Skills

Software Development

Algorithms and data structures

Algorithm implementation

Java, C, C++, Python, JS, OpenGL Programming

Interests

Software Development

Machine Learning / Deep Learning

Data Structures and Algorithms